smsnshayari.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy | SMSnShayari.com

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site http://www.smsnshayari.com . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this site.

**Information We Collect**

Every one is free to browse the www.smsnshayari.com site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the www.smsnshayari.com , unless you subscribe and agree to submit to us such information.

**Site Visit Information**

Just like any other website and web servers, our servers gather information on site activity, such as the reader’s domain name/IP address, referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL a reader visited prior to clicking through to our site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Vista machine).

We use this information on an aggregate, anonymous basis, to help us improve site content and target advertising. We may also disclose aggregated information (for example, the number of readers visiting a specific Web site section) to third parties. However, when we do present such aggregated site activity statistics to third parties, no one will be able to identify you personally or contact you.

**Links:**

Our site contains links to other sites, such as those of our advertisers and reference Web sites. We provide these links as a convenience to our readers. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability of the information.

We therefore encourage our readers to be aware when they leave our site. We strongly recommend that once you leave our site, you read the privacy policies of such other sites, as such other sites may collect information about you.

**Cookies**

A ‘cookie’ (a small data file) can be placed on your computer when you visit certain Web sites. Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a Web site, or information that allows the customization of a Web site for your use.

NUNU.in may use cookies to collect and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to help us improve the site content.

In the case of adverts appearing on our site, advertising cookies may be sent by third-part servers. This is standard practice in the Internet industry and is used to allow advertisers to track your response to the advertisements placed on our site.

These cookies do not identify you personally, do not enable third parties to access any information about you, and are used solely for the purpose of either site improvement research, or for proper merchant-partner crediting.

Note however that clicking on an advert link will take you to a third-party Web site. Advertisers and partners Web sites may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of those cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

Cookies and ‘Ads by Google’

Part of the adverts appearing on our site are posted by Google; these can be identified by the slogan ‘Ads by Google’.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses DoubleClick DART cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to better serve you with adverts that may be more relevant to you, based on your visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. You can even manage the areas of interest via the [Google Ads Preferences Manager](http://google.com/ads/preferences) to improve the relevance of ads posted by Google when you visit its partner sites.

The user information collected by Google through this interest-based advertising is used in accordance with Google’s privacy policies. It will not identify you personally, nor do Google use any personally identifiable information to show interest-based ads.

Should you prefer, you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

For more information on Google’s privacy policy in relation to the Google Ads appearing on our and other Google partner sites, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html) for details.  
**E-mails:**

We will never sell, give, trade, or otherwise distribute in any manner at any time, your e-mail address and related personal information that you may enter in any of the online forms, appearing on our Web site. Furthermore:

_Site Newsletter_ : When you subscribe to our site’s Daily Updates’, your e-mail will be used solely to send you the Updates regarding new Content on site on daily basis , otherwise you will not receive any update unless there is no new content. These Daily Updates are sent with partnership of “Google Feedburner” which deliver daily updates for us to you. Once you subscribe to our Daily Updates, you may unsubscribe at any time; just follow the unsubscribe link found on each site e-zine and your e-mail address will be immediately removed from our database.

_Feedback/Contact form_ : The return e-mail address used when submitting enquirers seeking smsnshayari.com advice or commenting on this site, is used solely for replying to your query only. Once we reply to your submission, your contact information will be kept for a maximum period of three months in case there arise the need to follow up. Once this period is over, all contact details and any exchanged correspondence will be deleted.

_Content Invitation Submission Forms_ : Should you leave your contact details when submitting content  to us which you want to publish with us, we will never ever share your email address with anyone ever however we will show your name as SUBMITTER for which we have specified on content submission form, you may also wish us to include your orkut profile and other profile URL, we will also publish it unless you don’t want it to be. No other use will be made of your e-mail.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

SMSnShayari.com reserves the right to amend this privacy policy from time to time. Should there be a significant change in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site home page to notify our readers of the change.

Rest assured however that our fundamental commitment to protecting our readers’ privacy will not change; any changes made will be made with this guiding principle in mind.

**Agreeing to this Privacy Policy:**

If you do not agree to SMSnShayari.com Privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any of the services offered by this site. Your use of this site indicates acceptance in full of this privacy policy.

**Contact us:**

Should you ever need to contact us or you have any query or suggestion then you can contact us through email ie. support [at] smsnshayari . com or you can use web form to [CONTACT US ](http://www.smsnshayari.com/contact-us/).

Thank you.  
SMSnShayari.com  
Entertainment is Precious
